<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Agri Project</string>
    <string name="title_activity_home">Home</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string-array name="first_choices">
        <item>select to filter"</item>
        <item>Goat</item>
        <item>Sweet Potato</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="second_choices_goat">
        <item>select to filter"</item>
        <item>Food</item>
        <item>Disease</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="third_choices_goat">
        <item>select to filter"</item>
        <item>Nutrients</item>
        <item>Meals</item>


    </string-array>
    <string name="title_activity_settings">Settings</string>

    <!-- Strings related to Settings -->

    <!-- Example General settings -->
    <string name="pref_header_general">General</string>

    <string name="pref_title_social_recommendations">Enable social recommendations</string>
    <string name="pref_description_social_recommendations">Recommendations for people to contact
        based on your message history
    </string>

    <string name="pref_title_display_name">Display name</string>
    <string name="pref_default_display_name">John Smith</string>

    <string name="pref_title_add_friends_to_messages">Add friends to messages</string>
    <string-array name="pref_example_list_titles">
        <item>Always</item>
        <item>When possible</item>
        <item>Never</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="pref_example_list_values">
        <item>1</item>
        <item>0</item>
        <item>-1</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Example settings for Data & Sync -->
    <string name="pref_header_data_sync">Data &amp; sync</string>

    <string name="pref_title_sync_frequency">Sync frequency</string>
    <string-array name="pref_sync_frequency_titles">
        <item>15 minutes</item>
        <item>30 minutes</item>
        <item>1 hour</item>
        <item>3 hours</item>
        <item>6 hours</item>
        <item>Never</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="pref_sync_frequency_values">
        <item>15</item>
        <item>30</item>
        <item>60</item>
        <item>180</item>
        <item>360</item>
        <item>-1</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="list_preference_entries">
        <item>Entry 1</item>
        <item>Entry 2</item>
        <item>Entry 3</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="list_preference_entry_values">
        <item>1</item>
        <item>2</item>
        <item>3</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="multi_select_list_preference_default_value" />

    <string name="pref_title_system_sync_settings">System sync settings</string>

    <!-- Example settings for Notifications -->
    <string name="pref_header_notifications">Notifications</string>

    <string name="pref_title_new_message_notifications">New message notifications</string>

    <string name="pref_title_ringtone">Ringtone</string>
    <string name="pref_ringtone_silent">Silent</string>

    <string name="pref_title_vibrate">Vibrate</string>
    <string name="goat_nutrients">Goats are efficient browsers and prefer eating brushy plants along with some other woody and weedy plants found on the ranges. Goats are able to digest a large variety of fibre and roughage. The nutrient requirements of goats are determined by age, sex, breed, production system (dairy or meat), body size, climate and physiological stage. Feeding strategies should be able to meet energy, protein, mineral, and vitamin needs depending on the condition of the goats. Goats do not depend on intensive feeding systems except some supplemental feeding during growth, lactation, pregnancy and winter. Of course, when goats are in lactation for an extended period of time (i.e., 10 months), they will require supplemental feeding on a higher plane of nutrition (e.g., dairy quality second cut alfalfa hay and grain ration). Goats belong to the small ruminant group of animals and have no upper incisor or canine teeth but a dental pad instead. The rumen is the largest part of four stomach compartments with the capacity of roughly 2-6 pounds. Some bacteria and protozoa are normal habitants of the rumen which break down plant food into volatile fatty acids along with vitamins and amino acids. The daily feed intake of goats ranges from 3-4% of body weight as expressed in pounds (dry matter/head/day). The daily feed intake is influenced by body weight, % of dry matter in the feeds eaten (12-35% in forages, 86-92% in hays and concetrates), palatability, and physiological stage of the goats (growth, pregnancy, and lactation).</string>
    <string name="goat_feed_time">If you\'re starting a goat herd, you will know that goats require some knowledge to feed them right. Whether raising goats for meat, establishing a dairy herd, or just practicing sustainable living on your homestead, goats need attention to their nutrition to thrive. One good rule of thumb: don\'t make drastic changes to your goats\' diet all at once. Don\'t feed them large amounts of new food. Either of these practices can lead to a major digestive upset for your goats. Change their diets slowly, giving the bacteria in their rumen (their first stomach, made for the initial step in the digestion of the plants they eat) time to adjust.</string>
</resources>
